<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Learn about Hybrid Cloud Patterns on Hybrid Cloud Patterns</title><link>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/</link><description>Recent content in Learn about Hybrid Cloud Patterns on Hybrid Cloud Patterns</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hybrid Cloud Patterns</title><link>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/about/</guid><description>Hybrid Cloud Patterns Hybrid Cloud Patterns and the downstream Validated Patterns are a natural progression from reference architectures with additional value.</description></item><item><title>Patterns quick start</title><link>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/quickstart/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/quickstart/</guid><description>Patterns quick start Each pattern can be deployed using the command line. Check the values-*.yaml for changes that are needed before deployment.</description></item><item><title>Infrastructure</title><link>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/infrastructure/</guid><description>Infrastructure Background Each validated pattern has infrastructure requirements. The majority of the validated patterns will run Red Hat OpenShift while some parts will run directly on Red Hat Enterprise Linux or (RHEL), more likely, a version of RHEL called RHEL for Edge.</description></item><item><title>OpenShift General Sizing</title><link>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/ocp-cluster-general-sizing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/ocp-cluster-general-sizing/</guid><description>OpenShift General Sizing Recommended node host practices The OpenShift Container Platform node configuration file contains important options. For example, two parameters control the maximum number of pods that can be scheduled to a node: podsPerCore and maxPods.</description></item><item><title>RHEL for Edge General Sizing</title><link>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/rhel-for-edge-general-sizing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/rhel-for-edge-general-sizing/</guid><description>RHEL for Edge General Sizing Recommended node host practices TBD</description></item><item><title>Using the Validated Pattern operator</title><link>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/using-validated-pattern-operator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/using-validated-pattern-operator/</guid><description>Using the Validated Pattern Operator Background The Validated Pattern Operator was developed in order to take advantage of the automation provided with the validated pattern framework.</description></item><item><title>Workflow</title><link>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/workflow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/workflow/</guid><description>Workflow These patterns are designed to be composed of multiple components, and for those components to be used in gitops workflows by consumers and contributors.</description></item><item><title>Implementation Requirements</title><link>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/implementation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/implementation/</guid><description>Technical Requirements Additional requirements specific to the implementation for all Community, and Validated patterns
Must Patterns MUST include one or more Git repositories, in a publicly accessible location, containing configuration elements that can be consumed by the OpenShift GitOps operator (ArgoCD) without supplying custom ArgoCD images.</description></item><item><title>Community Patterns</title><link>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/community/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/community/</guid><description>Community Pattern Requirements tl;dr What are they: Best practice implementations conforming to the Validated Patterns implementation practices Purpose: Codify best practices and promote collaboration between different groups inside, and external to, Red Hat Creator: Customers, Partners, GSIs, Services/Consultants, SAs, and other Red Hat teams Requirements General requirements for all Community, and Validated patterns</description></item><item><title>Validated Patterns</title><link>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/validated/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/validated/</guid><description>Validated Pattern Requirements tl;dr What are they: Technical foundations, backed by CI, that have succeeded in the market and Red Hat expects to be repeatable across customers and segments.</description></item><item><title>Secrets</title><link>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/secrets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/secrets/</guid><description>Infrastructure Background Enterprise applications require security, especially in multi-cluster and multi-site environments. Applications require trust and use certificates and other secrets in order to establish and maintain trust.</description></item><item><title>HashiCorp Vault</title><link>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/vault/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/vault/</guid><description>Deploying HashiCorp Vault in a validated pattern Prerequisites You have deployed/installed a validated pattern using the instructions provided for that pattern.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hybrid-cloud-patterns.io/learn/faq/</guid><description>FAQ What is a Hybrid Cloud Pattern? Hybrid Cloud Patterns are collections of applications (in the ArgoCD sense) that demonstrate aspects of hub/edge computing that seem interesting and useful.</description></item></channel></rss>