<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Learn about Validated Patterns on Validated Patterns</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/</link><description>Recent content in Learn about Validated Patterns on Validated Patterns</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Validated Patterns</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/about-validated-patterns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/about-validated-patterns/</guid><description>Overview of Validated Patterns Validated Patterns are an advanced form of reference architectures that offer a streamlined approach to deploying complex business solutions.</description></item><item><title>Validated Pattern tiers in depth</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/about-pattern-tiers-types/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/about-pattern-tiers-types/</guid><description>Validated Pattern tiers in-depth Patterns are categorized into distinct tiers: Sandbox, Tested, and Maintained.
The different tiers of Validated Patterns are designed to facilitate ongoing maintenance, support, and testing efforts for a pattern.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started with Multicloud GitOps</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/getting-started-multi-cloud-gitops/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/getting-started-multi-cloud-gitops/</guid><description>Getting Started with Multicloud GitOps Multicloud GitOps is a foundational pattern that demonstrates GitOps principles for managing applications across multiple clusters.</description></item><item><title>Patterns quick start</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/quickstart/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/quickstart/</guid><description>Patterns quick start overview This validated pattern quickstart offers a streamlined guide to deploying predefined, reliable configurations and applications, ensuring they meet established standards.</description></item><item><title>Configuring secrets</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/getting-started-secret-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/getting-started-secret-management/</guid><description>What are secrets Sensitive information referred to as secrets should not be exposed publicly or handled insecurely. This can include passwords, private keys, certificates (particularly the private parts), database connection strings, and other confidential data.</description></item><item><title>Validated pattern structure</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/vp_openshift_framework/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/vp_openshift_framework/</guid><description>OpenShift framework fundamentals The OpenShift validated patterns framework uses OpenShift GitOps (ArgoCD) as the primary driver for deploying patterns and keeping them up to date.</description></item><item><title>Structuring a validated pattern</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/vp_structure_vp_pattern/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/vp_structure_vp_pattern/</guid><description>Creating a validated pattern The high level steps to create a validated pattern are as follows:
Identify the business case you want to address.</description></item><item><title>Ansible GitOps Framework</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/vp_agof/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/vp_agof/</guid><description>About the Ansible GitOps framework (AGOF) for validated patterns The Ansible GitOps Framework provides an extensible framework to do GitOps with Ansible Automation Platform (AAP).</description></item><item><title>Using the Controller Configuration collection</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/vp_agof_config_controller/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/vp_agof_config_controller/</guid><description>Overview of the Ansible GitOps Framework (AGOF) Installation Process The Ansible GitOps Framework (AGOF) is a powerful solution designed to automate the deployment and configuration of Ansible Automation Platform (AAP) environments using GitOps principles.</description></item><item><title>Adding Operators to the framework</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/vp_add_ops_to_pattern/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/vp_add_ops_to_pattern/</guid><description>Adding Operators to the validated pattern framework Subscriptions are defined in the values files and they are OpenShift Operator subscriptions from the Operator Hub.</description></item><item><title>Adding a specific operator to hub values file</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/vp_add_specific_ops_to_pattern/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/vp_add_specific_ops_to_pattern/</guid><description>Procedure: Changing Subscription to Use a specific Operator Version This procedure outlines the steps to change an Operator subscription to use a specific version by updating the csv field and configuring the installation approval process.</description></item><item><title>Key concepts</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/keyconcepts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/keyconcepts/</guid><description>Key concepts This section describes a set of key concepts essential for creating validated pattern. This material provides you with foundational knowledge to get familiar with the validated patterns framework.</description></item><item><title>Validated patterns frameworks</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/validated_patterns_frameworks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/validated_patterns_frameworks/</guid><description>Introduction Validated patterns provides two frameworks to deploy applications: the OpenShift-based Validated Patterns framework and the Ansible GitOps Framework (AGOF).</description></item><item><title>Importing a cluster</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/importing-a-cluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/importing-a-cluster/</guid><description>Importing a managed cluster Many validated patterns require importing a cluster into a managed group. These groups have specific application sets that will be deployed and managed.</description></item><item><title>OpenShift General Sizing</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/ocp-cluster-general-sizing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/ocp-cluster-general-sizing/</guid><description>OpenShift General Sizing Recommended node host practices The OpenShift Container Platform node configuration file contains important options. For example, two parameters control the maximum number of pods that can be scheduled to a node: podsPerCore and maxPods.</description></item><item><title>Infrastructure</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/infrastructure/</guid><description>Background Each validated pattern has infrastructure requirements. The majority of the validated patterns will run Red Hat OpenShift while some parts will run directly on Red Hat Enterprise Linux or (RHEL), more likely, a version of RHEL called RHEL for Edge.</description></item><item><title>Using the Validated Patterns Operator</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/using-validated-pattern-operator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/using-validated-pattern-operator/</guid><description>About the Validated Patterns Operator You can use the Validated Patterns Operator to install and manage Validated Patterns. Use the Red Hat Hybrid Cloud Console to install the Validated Patterns Operator.</description></item><item><title>ClusterGroup in Values Files</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/clustergroup-in-values-files/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/clustergroup-in-values-files/</guid><description>ClusterGroup configuration in values files ClusterGroup serves as a centralized control mechanism, enabling the grouping of clusters based on specific criteria such as geographic location, project, or application type.</description></item><item><title>Workflow</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/workflow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/workflow/</guid><description>Workflow Patterns are designed to be composed of multiple components, that consumers and contributors can integrate into GitOps workflows. For instance, the Industrial Edge pattern comprises a repository with pattern-specific logic and configuration, alongside a common repository containing elements common to various patterns.</description></item><item><title>Secrets management in the Validated Patterns framework</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/secrets-management-in-the-validated-patterns-framework/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/secrets-management-in-the-validated-patterns-framework/</guid><description>Overview of secrets management Secrets management is a critical aspect of software development, especially when dealing with sensitive information such as passwords, API keys, and tokens.</description></item><item><title>HashiCorp Vault</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/vault/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/vault/</guid><description>Deploying HashiCorp Vault in a validated pattern Prerequisites You have deployed/installed a validated pattern using the instructions provided for that pattern.</description></item><item><title>Values Files</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/values-files/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/values-files/</guid><description>Exploring values A value represents a specific configuration or parameter that influences the behavior of a validated pattern. These values may range from simple settings like port numbers to more complex elements such as host names and DNS entries.</description></item><item><title>Secrets</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/secrets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/secrets/</guid><description>Secrets Secret Management One area that has been impacted by a more automated approach to security is in the secret management.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/faq/</guid><description>FAQ What is a Validated Pattern? Validated Patterns are collections of applications (in the ArgoCD sense) that demonstrate aspects of hub/edge computing that seem interesting and useful.</description></item></channel></rss>