<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Learn about Validated Patterns on Validated Patterns</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/</link><description>Recent content in Learn about Validated Patterns on Validated Patterns</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Validated Patterns</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/about/</guid><description>Validated Patterns and upstream Community Patterns are a natural progression from reference architectures with additional value. Here is a brief video to explain what patterns are all about:</description></item><item><title>Patterns quick start</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/quickstart/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/quickstart/</guid><description>Patterns quick start Each pattern can be deployed using the command line. The only requirement is to have git and podman installed.</description></item><item><title>Importing a cluster</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/importing-a-cluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/importing-a-cluster/</guid><description>Importing a managed cluster Many validated patterns require importing a cluster into a managed group. These groups have specific application sets that will be deployed and managed.</description></item><item><title>Infrastructure</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/infrastructure/</guid><description>Background Each validated pattern has infrastructure requirements. The majority of the validated patterns will run Red Hat OpenShift while some parts will run directly on Red Hat Enterprise Linux or (RHEL), more likely, a version of RHEL called RHEL for Edge.</description></item><item><title>OpenShift General Sizing</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/ocp-cluster-general-sizing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/ocp-cluster-general-sizing/</guid><description>Recommended node host practices The OpenShift Container Platform node configuration file contains important options. For example, two parameters control the maximum number of pods that can be scheduled to a node: podsPerCore and maxPods.</description></item><item><title>RHEL for Edge General Sizing</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/rhel-for-edge-general-sizing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/rhel-for-edge-general-sizing/</guid><description>Recommended node host practices TBD</description></item><item><title>Using the Validated Patterns Operator</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/using-validated-pattern-operator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/using-validated-pattern-operator/</guid><description>You can use the Validated Patterns Operator to install and manage Validated Patterns. Use the Red Hat Hybrid Cloud Console to install the Validated Patterns Operator.</description></item><item><title>Workflow</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/workflow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/workflow/</guid><description>These patterns are designed to be composed of multiple components, and for those components to be used in gitops workflows by consumers and contributors.</description></item><item><title>Implementation Requirements</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/implementation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/implementation/</guid><description>Technical Requirements Additional requirements specific to the implementation for all Community, and Validated patterns
Must Patterns MUST include one or more Git repositories, in a publicly accessible location, containing configuration elements that can be consumed by the OpenShift GitOps operator (ArgoCD) without supplying custom ArgoCD images.</description></item><item><title>Community Patterns</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/community/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/community/</guid><description>tl;dr What are they: Best practice implementations conforming to the Validated Patterns implementation practices
Purpose: Codify best practices and promote collaboration between different groups inside, and external to, Red Hat</description></item><item><title>Validated Patterns</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/validated/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/validated/</guid><description>tl;dr What are they: Technical foundations, backed by CI, that have succeeded in the market and Red Hat expects to be repeatable across customers and segments.</description></item><item><title>Secrets</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/secrets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/secrets/</guid><description>Background Enterprise applications require security, especially in multi-cluster and multi-site environments. Applications require trust and use certificates and other secrets in order to establish and maintain trust.</description></item><item><title>HashiCorp Vault</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/vault/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/vault/</guid><description>Prerequisites You have deployed/installed a validated pattern using the instructions provided for that pattern. This should include setting having logged into the cluster using oc login or setting you KUBECONFIG environment variable and running a make install.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://validatedpatterns.io/learn/faq/</guid><description>What is a Hybrid Cloud Pattern? Hybrid Cloud Patterns are collections of applications (in the ArgoCD sense) that demonstrate aspects of hub/edge computing that seem interesting and useful.</description></item></channel></rss>